iclr.cc 2018-09-04

# ICLR Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy explains how information is collected, used, and disclosed by the International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR), with respect to your access and use of our services, through our website (“Website”) or in connection with third party services.

#### Information We Collect and How We Use It

We collect certain information from you through your use of the Website, such as the information you provide to ICLR by registering for a user account.  

We want you to be comfortable using the Website so we have described in detail below what information we collect and how it is used.

#### Information You Provide to Us

When you use ICLR Website and register for a user account, limited information is collected about you through a simple form. This information is for the purpose of identifying and communicating with supporters, conference registrants and community members. 

We may need to send you announcements and account-related messages.  These will be sent through the Website or by email.

#### How We Share Your Information with Others

We will not share the personal information we have collected from you, except as described below:

  * when you give us your consent to do so, for example, when we tell you that the information you provide will be shared in some way and you provide us that information;
  * when we believe we are authorized or legally required to do so or that doing so is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including things like subpoenas, warrants or court orders;
  * to enforce or apply our Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use or our other policies or agreements.
  * if your company is one of our sponsors. Sponsors have access to a report that shows who from their company is attending (including email addresses), what they've registered for, and what they're presenting.

#### Accessing Your Information

If you would like ICLR to delete your personal information that has been collected, please contact us with your request. We will take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records and as otherwise required by law.

#### How We Protect Your Information

We employ administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, despite those efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.

#### Links to Other Sites

The ICLR Website may contain links to other services, apps, and sites not operated by us (we refer to these as "Other Sites"). Any information you provide on those Other Sites is provided directly to whoever owns that site and is subject to their privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to those Other Sites, and we are not responsible for the content you provide to, or the privacy and security practices and policies of, Other Sites.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Any information that is collected is subject to our Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our Privacy Policy from time-to-time. In the event of a modification to the Privacy Policy, ICLR will send notification to you that a change has occurred via the Website or Email. It is required that you accept the revised Privacy Policy before continuing to use the Website. By accepting changes to the policy, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy. 

#### Questions or Concerns

Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy.
